BRANCH INSPECTION
（分行稽核班）
Hello, Ayana?
喂，彩奈嗎？
I know. Seven o'clock tonight, right?
我知道，今晚7點吧？
Let's get together with the girls
我們幾個女生好好聚聚
and eat lots of delicious food.
享受很多美食
I'm excited.
好期待呀
About that…
關於那個嘛
can I bring my boyfriend along?
我可以帶我男朋友去嗎？
-Sure. -Also.
-當然好 -還有
There's someone I want to introduce you to.
我想介紹一個人讓妳認識
Someone you want to introduce me to? A guy?
什麼？介紹人…該不會是男人？
Of course! See you at seven.
當然囉，7點見
Ah, wait! Hey…
等一下…
I was wondering what your private phone call was about,
我就在想那通私人電話在聊什麼
but it was to plan a mixer party?
是在計畫聯誼啊
No, it wasn't! I was just…
才不是，我只是…
Well, it's about time you got yourself a boyfriend.
妳也該找個男朋友了
It's not what you think.
不是你想的那樣
That's right. Hanasaki.
沒錯，花咲
Look at this.
看看這個
What is this, Mr. Shibasaki?
芝崎次長，這是什麼？
A questionnaire by 100 female bank employees?
“一百位女性銀行員問卷調查”？
Yes, and look here.
沒錯，妳看這裡
Most female bank employees get married by 27 at the latest.
“大部分女銀行員 最晚在27歲結婚
When you turn 30 years old, men rarely ask you out anymore.
30歲以後 很少有男人會跟妳約會”
-I'm out of time. -I told you.
-我沒時間了 -我告訴過妳了
No, no. These are just statistics.
不，這些只是統計數據
So I'm fine.
我沒問題的
"Women who act strong and think that they'll be okay,
“表現堅強而且自認沒問題的女人
won't be able to find a boyfriend." End of quote.
將無法找到男朋友”，引述結束
Hanasaki. You should be honest.
花咲，誠實至上！
-Please take care of this. -Okay.
-請處理這個 -好的
Hanasaki is running out of time, huh?
花咲沒時間了
Why do I need him to tell me that?
為什麼要他來告訴我那個？
Mr. Shibasaki is always out to help people.
芝崎先生總是熱心助人
He and his wife love to play matchmaker.
他和他老婆喜歡撮合別人
Soon enough…
很快地
they might try to match you up with someone.
他們可能會幫妳撮合某個人
Matchmaking… no…
撮合？才不需要
I will find someone on my own.
我會自己找的
Are you going to the mixer party in that outfit?
妳打算穿那樣去參加聯誼嗎？
Well… I thought it was going to be a laid back dinner with girlfriends.
我以為是和女性朋友的輕鬆聚餐
That's a little too plain for a mixer party.
那樣穿去聯誼太樸素了
-You're right. -Yeah.
-你說的對 -是
I wore a uniform when I was a teller,
當櫃員要穿制服
so I always changed into clothes that I preferred…
所以，我都會換穿我準備的衣服…
I said it's not a mixer party!
我說了，那不是聯誼
Well, if you're really looking for a boyfriend,
如果妳真的想找男朋友
I think it's best to go home and change.
我認為妳最好回家換一套衣服
I will not change!
我才不換！
Or so I said, but…
雖然我那麼說，可是
I hope I don't look like I tried too hard.
希望看起來不會太刻意
It's all because of what Mr. Soma said.
都是因為相馬先生的話
Welcome.
歡迎光臨
-Please follow me. -Okay.
-請跟我來 -好的
Over here.
請往這邊
Oh, Ayana. Sorry to make you wait.
彩奈，抱歉久等了
You're late. What were you doing?
妳真慢，妳在幹嘛啊？
-I'm sorry. -Mai.
-對不起 -舞
You haven't met Yuuki in a while, right?
妳和由貴很久沒見面了吧？
-Hello.
-妳好 -你好
You're lovey-dovey as always.
你們還是一如往常地愛放閃
-What? -No, we're not.
-哪有？ -我們才沒有
-No, right? -Yeah.
-沒有，對吧？ -對
Oh, and what is this about introducing me to someone?
對了，要介紹人給我認識 是怎麼回事？
Ever since you broke up with your boyfriend earlier this year,
因為今年初，妳和妳男朋友分手後
you haven't found anyone new, and you've lost that spark.
就沒找到新的，妳都失去光彩了
Sorry for not having a spark.
我黯然無光，還真抱歉
I never asked you to help me find some--
可是，我沒有請妳幫我找…
But we found you a great person.
可是，我們幫妳找了一個很棒的人
-He's Yuuki's senior. -Yeah, he's really good looking.
-他是由貴的學長 -對，他長得非常好看
-What? -It'll make you wonder.
-什麼啊？ -會讓妳納悶
About where this gem was hiding all this time.
這顆寶石這麼久以來都藏在哪裡
A gem, huh?
寶石啊
-He's here. -What?
-他到了 -啊？
Hello.
學長
I'm sorry for being late.
抱歉來晚了
Mai, this is Mr. Tomoda.
舞，這位是友田先生
Nice to meet you. I'm Kojiro Tomoda.
很高興認識妳，我是友田浩次郎
Nice to meet you, I'm Mai Hanasaki.
很高興認識你，我是花咲舞
All right!
好耶
It's delicious.
好好吃喔
Do you like it? I'm so glad.
好吃嗎？太好了
-How about more wine? -Thank you.
-再來一點酒吧 -謝謝
This is a lovely restaurant, and everything is delicious.
這間餐廳真漂亮，而且東西都好好吃
It sure is.
沒錯
This Roquefort cheese sauce
這個洛克福乳酪醬
goes well with the meat.
和肉很搭
That looks so good.
看起來好好吃
-I want some too. -Sure.
-我也想要一點 -沒問題
-Thanks. -Me too.
-謝謝 -我也要
Mr. Tomoda, do you come to these restaurants pretty often?
友田先生常來這類餐廳嗎？
I come here every day.
這裡我每天都來
You eat steak every day?
你每天吃牛排？
He looks fresh, but he's probably the aggressive type…
他看起來爽朗，但大概是很猛的那型
No, Mai. This is Mr. Tomoda's restaurant.
不是啦，舞，這是友田先生的餐廳
What? Oh… that means he's the owner of Tokyo Dallas?
什麼？妳是說 他是東京達拉斯的老闆？
Yes, he's the president.
是啊，他是這裡的社長
I'm sorry for not saying it earlier.
抱歉，我沒早點說
Not at all.
沒關係
You have more, right?
你還有其他店，對吧？
He has a place in Akasaka and Nakameguro.
他在赤坂和中目黑有餐廳
I plan to keep on expanding as well.
我還打算繼續展店
-You're amazing. -Not at all.
-你真厲害 -沒有啦
I just want a lot of people to eat delicious steak.
我只是希望讓很多人吃到美味牛排
That's all.
如此而已
That's wonderful.
真是太好了
Excuse me, sir.
社長，打擾了
The Takahashi party coming in at nine is bringing more people,
9點高橋的派對要來更多人
so there won't be enough bisque.
法式濃湯會不夠
Then change the bisque to lobster
那就將法式濃湯改成龍蝦
and add crab to it.
再加蟹肉進去
Okay, I understand.
是，我懂了
-Oh, Otsuka. -Yes.
-對了，大塚 -是
Please reserve two servings of the sorbet.
請保留兩份雪酪
Oh, okay.
好的
The popular desserts always run out.
最受歡迎的甜點總是不夠
Thank you very much.
多謝你了
Excuse me.
我失陪了
I'm sorry about that.
真抱歉
When training young staff members,
訓練年輕工作人員時
there are lots of things that can only be taught on site.
很多事情都只能現場教
Managing a business must be a very difficult job.
不會啦，經營生意一定很不容易
-Ms. Mai, what do you do for work? -Oh, I'm…
-對了，舞是做什麼工作呢？ -我是…
Mr. Tomoda, I never told you?
友田先生，我沒告訴你嗎？
Mai works at the same place as me. Tokyo Daiichi Bank.
舞和我一樣在東京第一銀行
Is that right?
原來是這樣啊
If Ms. Mai was there, I'd visit that bank every day.
如果是舞在的銀行，我會每天都去
Every day… oh, please!
每天啊？什麼每天…拜託！
Actually, I've been using Tokyo Daiichi Bank ever since
其實，從我開第一間餐廳起
I opened my first restaurant.
往來的就是東京第一銀行
Oh, really?
真的嗎？
It seems like we're meant to be.
看來我們是命中注定
Yes!
是
I'm back!
我回來了
Welcome back.
妳回來啦
-Do you want dinner? -No.
-要吃晚餐嗎？ -不用
I'm full from eating delicious steak.
我吃美味牛排吃飽了
Where's the restaurant with delicious steak?
那個美味牛排餐廳在哪裡？
Mr. Soma.
相馬先生
You changed! You're even wearing pink shoes!
妳換衣服了，甚至穿了粉紅色鞋子
Stop eating dinner here.
別再來這裡吃晚餐了
Hey, stop interfering with my business.
喂，不要干擾我的生意
Mr. Soma is our valued customer.
相馬先生是我們的貴客
-Here's the shrimp dumpling. -Thank you.
-蝦餃來了 -謝謝
-Looks delicious. -Mai, do you want some too?
-看起來好好吃 -舞，妳也要吃一點嗎？
I told you that I'm full.
我說我吃飽了
It's delicious.
好吃
So how was the mixer party?
那個聯誼怎麼樣了？
You went to a mixer party?
妳去參加聯誼？
No, I didn't!
我沒有
I can find a nice man without going to a mixer party.
不參加聯誼我也能找到好男人
And how was he?
他是怎樣的人？
Well, he had a nice smile, and he's mature
他笑容溫和，個性成熟
but he has a boyish charm…
可是，他有孩子氣的魅力
-It's none of your business. -Okay.
-跟你沒關係 -好
I see. You met a nice man, huh?
我知道了，妳遇到了好男人
I see.
我知道了
Dad, you're always telling me to find a man and get married.
爸，你一直要我找個男人結婚
I know that,
我知道
but when it's really happening…
可是，真的發生時…
Mr. Soma, raising a daughter on your own is lonely and sad.
相馬先生，獨自撫養女兒孤單又傷心
You have my sympathy. Let me pour you a drink.
我同情你，我替你斟一杯
Thanks.
謝謝
Dad…
爸
You're kind of a pain.
你有點討厭
Thank you for the meal last night.
謝謝昨天的晚餐
I'd like to go eat the delicious steak again.
我希望再去吃一次美味牛排
Am I being too forward?
我會太過直接嗎？
Oh no.
不要
Are you okay?
妳沒事吧？
You look really crazy, getting excited on your own.
妳很誇張，在那裡自嗨
I'm not excited.
我沒有自嗨
I'm just sending a message to say thanks.
我只是傳簡訊去道謝
It's good manners.
這是禮貌
I wonder.
是這樣嗎？
It's the phone.
電話響了
What?
怎樣？
Swallow it.
吞下去
Fine, I'll take it.
好啦，我接
Hello, this is Branch Inspection.
您好，稽核班
What?
什麼？
I'll send her down right away.
我立刻要她下去
You have a guest.
妳有訪客
A guest? For me?
找我的訪客？
Someone from Tokyo Dallas.
某個“東京達拉斯”來的人
Tokyo Dallas.
東京達拉斯
What? Mr. Tomoda came to see me.
友田先生來找我？
Hold on…
等等
Wait a minute… um…
等一下
I'll be off.
我走了
She's definitely not okay.
她肯定有事
I wonder where Mr. Tomoda is.
友田先生在哪裡呢？
-Excuse me. -Yes?
-請問… -是
I'm from Tokyo Dallas.
我是從東京達拉斯來的
Oh!
喔
Excuse me.
我失陪了
You were at the restaurant…
你是在餐廳的那位…
Yes, I'm Otsuka.
對，我是大塚
Oh, so you're my guest… okay…
原來訪客是你啊
You forgot this.
妳忘了這個
I'm so sorry. Thank you very much.
真抱歉，多謝你了
You came all the way here to deliver this?
你專程送來給我嗎？
Um…
那個…
there's something I want to discuss.
有件事情我想找妳談
It's about our president.
是關於我們社長的
What?
什麼？
BRANCH INSPECTION
（分行稽核班）
Our employee is receiving dirty cash from a customer?
我們的員工收受客戶的非法資金？
Yes. Apparently, someone from the Shinagawa Branch
對，顯然是品川分行裡的某個人
received a bribe from
從一個叫東京達拉斯的公司
a company called Tokyo Dallas.
收受賄款
I overheard
我無意中聽到
my boss talking to the banker on the phone.
我老闆和那個銀行員講電話
The loan will be approved, right?
貸款會通過，對吧？
That's why I gave you two million yen.
所以我才給你兩百萬日圓
Yes, please make sure to take care of it.
對，請務必關照
I don't know who he paid the money to,
我不知道他把錢給了誰
but I'm sure that he paid two million yen to
但我確定他付給東京第一行某個人
someone at Tokyo Daiichi Bank.
兩百萬日圓
If that's true, that's a very serious issue.
如果是真的，那是很嚴重的問題
Yes.
沒錯
Mr. Otsuka, why are you telling us this?
大塚先生，你為什麼要告訴我們呢？
Oh… well…
那是因為…
Are you blowing the whistle on your boss?
你要揭發你的老闆？
No! If my boss is
不是的，如果我老闆
doing something illegal, I want him to stop right away.
正在做犯法的事，我希望他立刻停止
That's all.
只是這樣
President Tomoda hired me when I didn't have any education
友田社長雇用我時，我沒有學歷
or experience.
也沒有經驗
It's not just me.
不只是我
There are lots of employees who are grateful to him.
很多員工都非常感激社長
I see.
這樣啊
Please,
拜託了
save our restaurant.
救救我們餐廳
-Okay! -What?
-沒問題 -什麼？
We will do all we can to find the banker who accepted the two million yen,
我們會盡力找出收了 那兩百萬日圓的銀行員
and put an end to this!
終止犯罪行為！
H… hey, Hanasaki!
喂，花咲
-Right, Mr. Shibasaki? -What?
-對吧，芝崎次長？ -什麼？
Well… yeah.
嗯…是
This is a serious issue
這在我們銀行
for our bank.
是嚴重的問題
-Okay, let's investigate it. -We are?
-好，我們來調查 -要調查嗎？
Thank you very much!
麻煩你們了！
Here we go again.
又來了
Why do you it?
妳為什麼要自願
-Readily accept these troublesome cases? -Well…
-接下這種棘手的案子？ -那個嘛
How can we leave Mr. Otsuka after he begged us like that?
大塚先生那樣懇求，我們豈能不管？
-What? -Oh!
-什麼？ -啊
That means Mr. Tomoda
那就表示友田先生
was bribing the bank.
賄賂銀行啊
I thought I had met a nice guy
我還以為這麼久以來
for the first time in a long while.
第一次遇到好男人
I see.
原來
The restaurant you went to last night was Tokyo Dallas.
妳昨晚去的餐廳是東京達拉斯啊
Oh!
啊！
Yes.
對
I see.
這樣啊
Let's search Tokyo Dallas.
搜尋一下東京達拉斯
Kojiro Tomoda.
友田浩次郎
He's a good looking guy.
長得不錯
Stop that.
別這樣
It's true that the Shinagawa Branch
品川分行確實通過了
approved a loan for a company called Tokyo Dallas
給一間叫東京達拉斯的公司
for 50 million yen.
五千萬日圓的貸款
That means that President Tomoda paid two million yen to someone
那表示友田社長為了獲得貸款
at the Shinagawa Branch to get that loan?
付了兩百萬日元給某個品川分行的人
Most likely. This restaurant is
很有可能
expanding locations in the city, but their business was probably
這間餐廳正在東京展店 但是他們的生意
not doing well enough to get an approval for a loan.
大概不足以通過貸款
But it's unacceptable for the bank to accommodate
可是，銀行以收受金錢
a loan contract by getting money.
通過貸款合約是不被接受的
Please go to the Shinagawa Branch and secretly investigate who
請去品川分行秘密調查
accepted the bribe.
是誰接受賄賂
Yes, sir.
是
Good luck. I'm not liking this.
祝你們好運，我不喜歡這種事
I have to report this to management now.
我現在必須向上層報告這件事
I never imagined
我怎麼也想不到
that I would be investigating Tokyo Dallas.
我會調查東京達拉斯
You're the one that accepted this.
是妳接下這個案子的
You're right.
你說的對
But I understand that you're sad because you went on a rare date,
不過，我了解妳很難過 難得有個約會
and it ended up like this.
結果卻是這樣
Don't say that it's rare.
不要說“難得”這兩個字
All right, let's rest our minds and get to work.
好啦，我們收心工作了
Listen Hanasaki.
聽好了，花咲
Branch Manager Yagi at Shinagawa Branch
品川分行的經理八木
is a super elite who worked at headquarters for a long time.
是在總部工作非常久的超級菁英
It's not going to be easy.
這件事不容易處理
I'll be prepared.
我會準備好的
And one more thing.
還有一件事
Don't tell me…
別告訴我…
Shindo faction.
真藤派
I knew it… It's becoming even more troublesome.
我知道了，事情更加棘手了
Exactly.
沒錯
SHINAGAWA BRANCH
（品川分行）
BRANCH MANAGER YAGI
（分行經理，八木）
And what is Branch Inspection doing at our branch?
稽核員來我們分行有何貴幹？
We found some errors in some
我們在一些舊貸款文件中
of the old loan documents so we came
發現幾個錯誤
to check on them and to give guidance.
所以過來查看和給予指導
Branch Inspection must be very bored
稽核工作一定非常無聊
to come all the way here for that.
稽核員才會為此大老遠過來
-Right? -Exactly.
-是吧？ -正是
We will not take much of your time.
不會占用你們太多時間
Please show us some loan documents…
請讓我們看貸款文件…
There isn't a single thing wrong with our loans.
我們的貸款沒有絲毫錯誤
-But-- -The branch manager is being clear.
-可是… -分行經理說
We don't need you here.
這裡不需要你們
But still,
不過，儘管如此
we cannot go back without doing anything.
我們不能什麼都沒做就回去
Please cooperate.
敬請配合
First of all, does this young female employee
首先，這位年輕女行員
know anything about loans?
對貸款有任何了解嗎？
No, right?
沒有吧？
Um… with all due respect…
那個，恕我直言…
-Don't do it. -What?
-別說了 -什麼？
Well… since Branch Inspection has to do their job,
既然稽核員必須執行工作
let's have Section Chief Nanba deal with them.
就請融資課的難波課長來處理吧
Yes, let's do that.
就這麼辦吧
Please make it very quick.
請盡快完成
Unlike Branch Inspection, our branch is very busy.
分行不像稽核班，我們是非常忙的
Goodbye.
再見
What a jerk.
真是個混蛋
I bet the one taking the bribe is that branch manager.
我敢說收受賄賂的就是分行經理
Don't accuse him just yet.
還不能指控他
But he's so suspicious.
但是他很可疑
"There isn't a single thing wrong with our loans."
“我們的貸款沒有絲毫錯誤”
Those are the ones that are filled with problems.
那就是有問題的人會說的話
Listen Hanasaki.
聽好，花咲
Branch Manager isn't the only one
分行經理並不是唯一
who has a say with loans.
有權決定貸款的人
The deputy branch manager and section chief do too.
副理和融資課長也可以
Calm down.
冷靜下來
Apparently, there is a banker
顯然是有一個品川分行的銀行員
in the Shinagawa Branch that accepted illegal funds.
收受了非法資金
Shinagawa Branch…
品川分行
-Is that where Yagi is? -Yes.
-八木在那裡，是嗎？ -是
If that's true…
如果是事實
it would be a big blow to the Shinagawa Branch.
對品川分行將是很大的打擊
Yes.
是
The pair from Branch Inspection is there right now
那兩個稽核員現在就在那裡
to investigate.
進行調查
Branch Inspection?
稽核員？
You messed up her life.
你毀了她的人生
I will never forgive you for that.
我絕對不原諒你
That little brat…
那個臭女孩
She better not do anything unnecessary.
她最好不要做沒必要的事
Yes.
是
These are all the specified loan documents.
指定的貸款文件都在這裡
-Thank you for your cooperation. -Thank you.
-謝謝你的配合 -謝謝
Um…
那個…
Is there a problem with a company in one of these files?
這些文件中的哪家公司有問題嗎？
No, not at all.
不是的
We're just doing a quick check.
我們只是快速稽查
Yes, a quick check.
對，快速的
I see.
這樣啊
Then, I'll be leaving.
那麼我離開了
He seemed very concerned.
他似乎很焦慮
That section chief is definitely suspicious too.
那個課長肯定也很可疑
-Here it is. Tokyo Dallas. -Thanks.
-在這裡，東京達拉斯 -謝謝
Now, let's take a close look at this.
現在我們仔細看看
Okay.
好
But you know…
可是你知道嗎？
that restaurant seemed like it was doing really well.
那間餐廳似乎經營得很不錯
I wonder if they couldn't
我很訝異他們不靠賄賂
get a loan without paying a bribe…
無法通過貸款
Mr. Tomoda too…
友田先生也是
I thought he was a great guy.
我以為他是好人
Looks can be deceiving, huh.
人果然不能只看外表呢
You just have bad taste in men.
妳只是對男人的品味太差
Why are you replying?
你幹嘛那麼急著回話啊？
Just ignore me and carry on.
別管我，繼續
What are those branch inspectors investigating?
那兩個分行稽核員在調查什麼？
According to Mr. Nanba,
據難波先生說
they are checking close to 50 random loan documents.
他們正在檢查 將近50份隨機貸款文件
What?
什麼？
I'll ask Section Chief Nanba to keep a close eye on them.
我會請難波課長密切注意他們
Please do that.
去做吧
This is strange.
這就怪了
Did you find anything suspicious?
你有發現可疑的地方嗎？
No, it's strange because there isn't anything suspicious.
沒有，怪就怪在沒有任何可疑的地方
What?
什麼？
Tokyo Dallas isn't performing that badly.
東京達拉斯的表現沒那麼差
Their business was down at one point, but they recovered last summer.
他們的生意一度下滑 但是去年夏天恢復了
-They even came out of the red. -You're right.
-甚至脫離赤字 -你說的對
Then…
那麼…
A 50-million-yen loan wouldn't have been unreasonable.
五千萬日圓的貸款不會不合理
Then there's no reason for him to bribe the bank.
那麼他沒有理由賄賂銀行
Exactly.
沒錯
What does this mean?
這表示什麼？
This is great timing.
時機正好
-I felt like eating meat today. -What?
-我今天想吃肉 -什麼？
Let's go meet President Tomoda.
我們去見友田社長
Tokyo Dallas.
東京達拉斯
-We're going there? -Yeah.
-我們要去那裡嗎？ -對
Let's eat meat.
吃肉…
Wow, it's a nice restaurant.
這間餐廳真不錯
It's fancy.
很高級
-It's so awkward. -What?
-太尷尬了 -什麼？
To come here when I'm suspicious of Mr. Tomoda.
在我懷疑友田先生時來這裡
Wow.
哇
Steak from Tokyo Dallas is really popular right now.
東京達拉斯的牛排現在很受歡迎
Oh, they use the Musashi Japanese beef.
哦，他們使用武藏和牛
This is going to be good.
這個一定很不錯
Eating steak two days in a row is…
連續兩天吃牛排…
You don't have to eat it.
妳可以不吃
I'll eat it.
我要吃
Are you ready to order?
準備點餐了嗎？
I'll have the…
我要…
I ate this yesterday, but I'll order it again.
我昨天吃這個，今天要再點一次
The Dallas Special with the premium Musashi Japanese beef.
達拉斯特餐的最高級武藏和牛
I'll do the Dallas Special too.
我也要達拉斯特餐
What?
什麼？
-Two Dallas Specials? -Wait… hold on.
-兩客達拉斯特餐嗎？ -等一下
Hanasaki, you can't order this.
花咲，妳不能點這個
It costs 15,000 yen.
它要一萬五千日圓
Who cares, let's just order it.
我才不管，就點它了
Two Dallas Specials.
兩份達拉斯特餐
-Okay. -Thanks.
-好的 -謝謝
I wonder if I can expense this.
不知道經費還夠嗎？
If I can't, it'll be out of pocket.
不能的話，就得自掏腰包了
Thank you for treating me.
謝謝你請客
Ms. Mai. Welcome back.
舞，歡迎再度光臨
Thank you.
謝謝
I'm glad to see you here two days in a row.
真高興連續兩天在這裡見到妳
Good evening.
晚安
-This is? -Oh,
-這位是？ -喔
my name is Soma.
我姓相馬
I heard our Hanasaki came here yesterday.
聽說我們的花咲昨天來這裡
Our?
我們的？
He's my boss.
他是我的上司
Oh, at the bank?
喔，銀行的嗎？
I see.
這樣啊
Please have a seat.
請坐
Thank you.
謝謝
This is a great restaurant.
這間餐廳很棒
It seems like you're busy too.
你們似乎也很忙
Yes, thankfully.
是，很幸運
-Business seems to be doing well too. -Yes.
-生意好像很不錯 -是
Oh? How do you know that?
啊，你怎麼知道的？
We work in Branch Inspection, and we're visiting
我們在分行稽核班
the Shinagawa Branch right now.
目前正在訪視品川分行
We're inspecting the loan documents.
稽核貸款文件
Loans?
貸款？
I'm sorry I never mentioned this before.
抱歉，之前我沒提到這個
Branch Inspection visits various branches
稽核員要訪視各個分行
and checks for any problems.
檢查各種問題
Oh… I see.
原來如此
Um…
那個…
What exactly do you investigate about the loans?
你們會對貸款進行什麼稽核呢？
What we investigate?
稽核什麼…
In short, we check to make sure there are no problems
簡單來說，我們檢查貸款相關細節
with details regarding the loans.
確定沒有問題
I see…
這樣啊
I'll be heading back to work,
我要回去工作了
so, please enjoy.
請盡情享用
Delicious.
好吃
You're such an opportunist.
妳真會利用機會
You were saying that you didn't want steak two days in a row.
還說不想連著兩天吃牛排
What's delicious is delicious.
好吃的東西就是好吃
But…
可是
Mr. Tomoda is suspicious after all.
友田先生果然很可疑
He clearly became wary when we talked about the loan.
我們說到貸款時 他明顯變得小心翼翼
It means that he has something to hide.
表示他隱瞞了什麼事
I knew it.
我就知道
Mr. Tomoda is handing money to the bank.
友田先生果然有賄賂銀行員
Now,
現在
we have to figure out who accepted two million yen from him.
我們必須找出他把兩百萬日圓交給誰
Yes.
是
Branch Manager Yagi, Deputy Branch Manager Wakamura,
分行經理八木、副理若村
Section Chief Nanba.
融資課長難波
Let's investigate those three.
我們調查這三個人
TAKESHI NANBA
（交易明細，姓名：難波剛士）
We checked their accounts,
我們查了他們帳戶
but they didn't have any transfers from Tokyo Dallas.
但是都沒有從東京達拉斯匯過去的錢
A banker wouldn't leave any
銀行員接受賄賂
traces behind when they accept bribes.
不會留下任何蛛絲馬跡的
You're right.
你說的對
I checked the account used by Tokyo Dallas,
我查了東京達拉斯所使用的帳戶
but they didn't transfer anything to those three either.
也沒有給那三個人的任何匯款
I bet.
我打賭
There would be no trace if he paid in cash.
如果他付現金，就不會留下任何形跡
There's nothing we can do.
我們無能為力
What? Two million…
什麼？兩百萬…
What is it, Hanasaki?
花咲，那是什麼？
Two million yen was transferred as a payment in October.
10月時匯了兩百萬日圓作為付款
If it says payment, we don't know what it was used for.
如果說是付款 我們就不知道它的用途
-Mr. Soma, please take a look at this. -What?
-相馬先生，請看一下這個 -什麼？
There's an 840-yen service fee charged on the same day.
當天有一筆840日圓的手續費
Service fee?
手續費？
840 yen is the service fee when using a check.
840日圓是使用支票的手續費
I see.
我懂了
President Tomoda paid the bribe to Shinagawa Branch.
友田社長賄賂品川分行
-But he used a check. -Yes.
-用的是支票 -對
If he uses a check, it will only be marked as a payment
如果用支票 就只會在東京達拉斯的帳戶
on Tokyo Dallas' account.
註記付款
The person receiving it can easily cash that at any bank.
收到的人可以輕易在任何銀行兌現
It's perfect for a bribe.
用在賄賂太完美了
But unfortunately,
可是很不幸
we can't track it.
我們無法追蹤它
-Ah! -What is it now?
-啊！ -又怎麼了？
Cashed checks,
兌現的支票
always come back to the branch they were issued from.
都會回到開出支票的分行
Yeah.
沒錯
The check should have
那張支票上
a signature of the person who cashed it.
應該會有兌現者的簽名
-That's who took the bribe. -Yes.
-那就是收賄款的人 -對
Which bank did Tokyo Dallas use to issue the check?
東京達拉斯使用哪家銀行開出支票？
Branch number 194.
分行194
MEGURO BRANCH
（目黑分行）
-It's Meguro Branch. -Good job.
-目黑分行 -幹得好
MEGURO BRANCH
（目黑分行）
Here it is.
在這裡
-Thank you.
-謝謝
-Here it is. -Let's see.
-在這裡 -我們看看
Ryoji Wakamura.
若村良二
Deputy Branch Manager Wakamura.
分行副理若村
So it was him?
所以是他？
I didn't expect it to be him.
我沒想到會是他
I thought it was Branch Manager Yagi.
我以為是分行經理八木
But Branch Manager Yagi came from headquarters to the branch
不過，分行經理八木從總部調到分行
for the first time in ten years.
是十年來第一次
So Deputy Manager Wakamura was probably running the Shinagawa Branch.
所以管理品川分行的大概是若村副理
It's unacceptable for him to fill his own pockets with
他用不法錢財中飽私囊
dirty cash.
無法接受
-Let's go, Mr. Soma. -Yeah.
-相馬先生，我們走 -好
What are you saying?
你們說什麼？
I did not receive any money!
我沒有收任何錢
Are you going to play innocent?
你想裝無辜嗎？
It's unacceptable for a banker to receive illegal funds
銀行員向客戶收取非法資金
from a customer.
是無法接受的
Where's the proof?
證據在哪裡？
Hanasaki.
花咲
This
這個
is a check issued by Tokyo Dallas for two million yen.
是東京達拉斯開出的兩百萬日圓支票
Isn't this your signature?
這個不是你的簽名嗎？
That's…
那個是…
This is proof that you received
這個是你收了東京達拉斯
a two-million-yen bribe from Tokyo Dallas.
兩百萬日圓賄款的證據
You're wrong! I…
你們錯了，我…
I…
我…
I personally lent some money to Mr. Tomoda, so he paid me back
我個人借錢給友田先生
with that check.
他用那張支票還我錢
What…
什麼？
The business at Tokyo Dallas is going really well,
沒錯，東京達拉斯的生意非常好
so we can expect a lot from them.
我們可以抱持高度期待
If the loan was processed correctly, there's no problem, right?
如果貸款正確處理，不會有問題吧？
Listen. There are no problems with the loan
聽好，給東京達拉斯的貸款
for Tokyo Dallas.
沒有問題
Now, go away.
現在，快滾
-Wait Hanasaki… -But Mr. Soma!
-花咲，等等 -可是，相馬先生
What Deputy Manager Wakamura says is true.
副理若村說的是真的
Tokyo Dallas is performing well,
東京達拉斯的表現良好
so they shouldn't have problems getting a loan.
所以他們貸款不應該有問題
Which means we can't prove that
那就表示我們無法證明
this two million yen was used to
這兩百萬日圓
approve their loan.
是用來通過他們的貸款
Unless we figure out what this
除非我們釐清
money was paid for,
這個錢是用來支付什麼
we can't question Deputy Manager Wakamura any further.
否則我們不能進一步質問若村副理
But how can we figure that out?
但是，我們要怎樣釐清呢？
I'll go
我要再去
talk to Mr. Otsuka one more time.
和大塚先生談一次
There might be something he hasn't told us yet.
可能有他沒告訴我們的事
Yeah.
沒錯
Then I'll go to this place.
那麼我去這個地方
You're trying another gourmet spot at a time like this?
這種時候你還想吃美食？
Look.
妳看
A steakhouse established by Hidehiko Akiyama, who used to work at
“秋山英彥成立的鐵板燒餐廳
the popular restaurant Tokyo Dallas.
他曾經在人氣餐廳東京達拉斯工作”
Apparently, Chef Akiyama quit and left after a fight with President Tomoda.
顯然秋山主廚在和 友田社長爭執後辭職
He might know something, right?
他可能知道些什麼，對吧？
-I see. -I'm sorry.
-是這樣啊 -很抱歉
We thought we had him…
我們以為抓到他了
We were so close.
就差一點
Um…
那個…
do you have any idea as to why President Tomoda
你知道為什麼友田社長
gave two million yen
要給銀行
to the bank?
兩百萬日圓嗎？
What?
什麼？
There has to be some kind of a reason behind it.
背後一定有原因吧？
No… I don't know anything.
我什麼都不知道
I see.
是這樣啊
PRIME JAPANESE BLACK SIRLOIN
（上等黑毛和牛）
Sounds delicious.
感覺好好吃
It's delicious!
好吃
Thank you.
謝謝
I'm actually eating steak two days in a row.
事實上，我已經連續兩天吃牛排了
-You must like it. -Well…
-你一定很喜歡吃 -嗯
I'm…
對了，我是
Soma from Tokyo Daiichi Bank.
東京第一銀行的相馬
Mr. Akiyama,
秋山先生
you used to be in a restaurant called Tokyo Dallas, right?
你曾經待過一間 叫做東京達拉斯的餐廳，對吧？
Yes.
是
May I ask few questions about President Tomoda?
我可以問你一些 關於友田社長的問題嗎？
Why?
為什麼呢？
Well, an employee at Tokyo Dallas named Mr. Otsuka
東京達拉斯有個叫大塚的員工
is really worried about Mr. Tomoda,
非常擔心友田先生
so we've been lending our ears.
我們便聽他怎麼說
Otsuka is?
大塚嗎？
I see.
我知道了
Tomoda and I
我和友田
started with a restaurant as small as this one here.
一起開了像這間這麼小的餐廳
We took low-cost meat…
我們以低價肉…
This is good!
這個好
…and cooked it the best possible way.
…採最佳方式烹調
It might be better if it's rare…
如果它稀少，可能可以更好
We experimented every day,
我們兩個人每天實驗
learning by trial and error.
從嘗試錯誤中學習
Tomoda was savvy with business,
友田很懂做生意
so our business grew bigger.
所以我們的生意越做越大
But you left after a fight with Mr. Tomoda, right?
但是你在和友田先生 吵了一架之後離開了，對吧？
No, it was just a difference of opinion.
不是，我們只是意見不同
He was intent on expanding the locations,
他打算擴張據點
but I couldn't keep up with that plan.
但是我跟不上那個計畫
I see.
原來如此
I have nothing against Tomoda.
我並不反對友田
He has always been a diligent worker
他一直勤奮工作
and he's honest.
人也正直
That's enough.
夠了
Please stop the investigation.
請不要再調查了
What?
什麼？
I've been thinking…
我一直在想
whether telling you was the right thing to do.
告訴你們到底對不對
I feel like
總覺得
what I did was an act of betrayal.
我在背叛老闆
That's not true.
不是那樣的
Mr. Otsuka, you really wanted to help that restaurant, right?
大塚先生，你真的很想幫助餐廳吧？
I think that's commendable.
我認為那麼做令人欽佩
No, I…
不是，我…
Papa!
爸爸
Hey…
喔！
He's so cute.
好可愛
-How old is your son? -He's almost four.
-你兒子幾歲？ -快四歲了
I want to
為了我兒子
become a reliable chef, for the sake of my son.
我希望成為一個可信賴的廚師
I shouldn't continue on like this.
我不應該繼續這樣下去
It has to be a job that my family will be proud of.
必須是能讓家人引以為傲的工作
What?
什麼？
It's nothing.
沒什麼
I'll be going.
先失陪了
Come here, Keita.
啟太過來
All right!
好棒
So you didn't find anything either?
你也沒有任何發現嗎？
Yeah.
是
But there's something strange about Tokyo Dallas for sure.
不過東京達拉斯確實有奇怪之處
-What is? -Listen.
-哪裡奇怪？ -聽著
Usually, if the main chef leaves while your business
通常最重要的主廚
is in a slump,
在生意不好時離開
the business will get even worse, right?
生意會變得更糟，對吧？
-Yeah. -Not with Tokyo Dallas.
-對 -可是東京達拉斯
Their business went up after
在秋山先生離去後
Mr. Akiyama left.
生意變好了
It's so strange.
這太奇怪了
So that means something must have
意思是在秋山先生離開後
happened after Mr. Akiyama left.
一定有事情發生
Yeah.
對
There's something that bothers me too.
也有事情困擾我
What is it?
什麼事？
Mr. Otsuka said,
大塚先生說
"It has to be a job that my family will be proud of."
“必須是能讓家人 引以為傲的工作”
Is there something that bothers his conscience?
他的良心對什麼東西過意不去嗎？
I don't know…
我不知道
Here are the shrimp dumplings.
蝦餃來了
-Here it is. -Thanks.
-在這裡 -謝謝
How is it? Is it good?
如何？好吃嗎？
Yeah. Of course your shrimp dumplings are good.
爸的蝦餃當然好吃
To tell you the truth, the price for Shiba shrimp went up
告訴你們實話，白蝦價格上漲
but I didn't want to raise the cost of the dishes,
但是，我不想提高這道料理的售價
so I changed the shrimp to a more inexpensive one.
所以，我改用比較便宜的蝦子
Is that right?
是這樣嗎？
-It's delicious as always. -I'm glad to hear that.
-和以前一樣好吃 -真高興聽你這麼說
I come up with ways to maintain the quality even when using
我想出辦法維持住品質
low cost ingredients.
即便用便宜的食材
Don't worry, it's still delicious even with a different ingredient.
別擔心，即使用不同食材 還是一樣好吃
Ah!
啊！
-What is it? -You scared me with your loud voice.
-怎麼了？ -那麼大聲，嚇死我了
Mr. Soma.
相馬先生
I think I solved the mystery.
我想我解開謎團了
What?
什麼？
SHINAGAWA BRANCH
（品川分行）
Come in.
請進
Excuse me.
打擾了
What are you guys doing here?
你們來這裡做什麼？
Mr. Yagi, I came here to ask for your cooperation
八木先生，我來是請你配合
regarding the issue with Tokyo Dallas and Mr. Wakamura.
關於東京達拉斯與若村先生的問題
What?
什麼？
What are you saying? You will not have our cooperation.
你在說什麼？ 我們才不會配合你們！
That's not acceptable.
這樣可不行
Mr. Wakamura, you will have to answer everything truthfully.
若村先生，你必須樣樣據實回答
-Shut up. -No, I won't.
-閉嘴！ -我不要！
What?
什麼？
President.
社長
What is it?
什麼事？
There's… something I want to talk to you about.
我有事情想跟你說
Sorry, maybe a little later.
抱歉，等一下
Hello.
喂？
Ms. Mai.
是舞啊
What?
什麼？
What do you mean?
妳是什麼意思？
I'm sorry to bother you right before dinner hours.
很抱歉，正好在晚餐時段前來打擾
We're sorry.
很抱歉
What is it?
什麼事情？
What is this about the loans?
關於貸款是什麼意思？
We have no reason to be told by the bank--
銀行沒理由告知我們…
Mr. Tomoda.
友田先生
You paid two million yen of dirty money
你付了兩百萬日圓的非法資金
to Deputy Manager Wakamura.
給若村副理
What are you saying?
你在說什麼？
That was money that I had personally borrowed from Mr. Wakamura.
那是我個人向若村借的錢
Did Mr. Wakamura call you
若村先生打電話給你
so that your stories would match up?
讓你們的說詞能對得上嗎？
That's ridiculous.
這太荒謬了
Why would I have to pay him dirty money?
我為什麼要付給他非法資金？
Why would you?
你為什麼要呢？
Good question.
好問題
Business at Tokyo Dallas is doing well.
東京達拉斯的生意不錯
You should be able to get a loan without
你應該可以不必賄賂銀行
bribing the bank.
就貸得到錢
So why did you pay two million yen?
所以你為什麼要付兩百萬日圓呢？
Mr. Tomoda, you said that
友田先生，你說過
business at Tokyo Dallas is doing well,
東京達拉斯的生意不錯
but in fact that was
但事實上
a lie, right?
那是謊話，對吧？
You failed at expanding restaurant locations,
你展店失敗
so the business at Tokyo Dallas
所以東京達拉斯的生意
started going down two years ago.
兩年前開始下滑
But all of a sudden, business started to recover
但是突然間，從某個時間點起
from a certain point in time.
生意開始恢復
What happened?
發生了什麼事？
We did a thorough investigation of your restaurant.
我們對你的餐廳做了徹底調查
And we noticed something strange.
而且注意到奇怪的事
The buying price of the beef went down,
牛肉的進價下降
but there were no changes
但是菜單上的價格
to the prices on the menu.
卻沒有改變
What does this mean?
這表示什麼呢？
The change in the buying price
進價改變與生意恢復
and business recovery all happened last summer.
都在去年夏天
At the same time.
同時發生
Mr. Tomoda,
友田先生
you came up with a solution to recover
你想出一個辦法
your business performance.
恢復你的業績
A solution that someone in
一個餐飲界的人
the restaurant business should never resort to.
絕對不會訴諸的手段
Food fraud.
食品詐欺
The Dallas Special.
達拉斯特餐
That's not
並不是使用
Musashi Japanese beef, right?
武藏和牛，對吧？
We went to your supplier,
我們去找你的供應商
Kitamoto Seiniku, for information.
北本肉品提供資料
DELIVERY STATEMENT
（交貨單）
We checked all of the delivery statements.
我們核對了所有交貨單
There was no record
過去一年
of Musashi Japanese beef being delivered to Tokyo Dallas
沒有武藏和牛送至東京達拉斯
this past year.
的任何紀錄
Using low-cost ingredients in order to raise profit
使用低價食材以提高獲利
is natural for a business.
對企業是很自然的事
But selling low-cost meat
但是以低價肉品
as a brand-name meat is called
當成商標肉品來販售
food fraud and that is clearly
就叫食品詐欺
a rule violation.
顯然是違反規定
Mr. Wakamura
若村先生
noticed that fraud when he was considering the loan approval.
在考慮貸款批准時發現了食品詐欺
That two million yen
那兩百萬日圓
was not a bribe to receive a loan from the bank,
不是為了賄賂銀行以取得貸款
but it was to have him turn a blind eye regarding the food fraud.
而是要他對食品詐欺視而不見
It was hush money.
那是封口費
That's…
那個…
Deputy Branch Manager Wakamura admitted to everything.
若村副理全都招認了
He will receive strict
他會受到銀行
disciplinary action from the bank.
嚴格的紀律處分
Wait a minute.
等一下
Then what about the loan?
那個貸款會怎樣？
Will it get cancelled?
會被取消嗎？
Most likely.
很有可能
Then what will happen to my restaurant?
那我的餐廳要怎麼辦？
Isn't it natural for a business owner to
企業老闆避免生意垮台
prevent their business from collapsing?
不是天經地義的事嗎？
I only tried to…
我只是想要
protect my employees!
保護我的員工
What's wrong with that?
那有什麼錯？
With all due respect…
恕我直言
did you really think that you could protect everything
你真的認為你能靠詐欺
by using fraud?
保護一切嗎？
Because you chose to cheat by using food fraud,
因為你選擇利用食品詐欺作弊
this restaurant is now in a pinch,
現在這間餐廳到了緊要關頭
with only a slim chance of survival.
生存機會微乎其微
Mr. Tomoda.
友田先生
You did wrong as a business owner.
身為企業老闆，你做錯了
I'm
我…
finished.
完蛋了
I don't think you're finished yet.
我不認為你完蛋了
Mr. Tomoda.
友田先生
The person who came to us for help,
來找我們幫忙的人
is Mr. Otsuka.
是大塚先生
Otsuka?
大塚？
He betrayed me?
他背叛我？
You're wrong.
你錯了
He didn't say a single word about food fraud.
他對食品詐欺隻字未提
It must have pained Mr. Otsuka when he found out about
大塚先生發現食品詐欺時
the food fraud.
想必很痛苦
But if the bank started investigating the loan,
但是，銀行如果開始調查貸款
it might move you to stop the food fraud.
也許能讓你停止食品詐欺
That was his plan.
那是他的計畫
He was saying
他說
that he's so grateful to you,
他非常感激你
and that's why he wants to save this restaurant.
那是他想拯救這間餐廳的原因
No way…
不可能
Mr. Otsuka has so much faith in you.
大塚先生對你充滿信心
Will you leave him hopeless, and without a job?
你要讓他失去希望和工作嗎？
It's not just Mr. Otsuka.
不只大塚先生
Every single person who works here
在這裡工作的每一個人
has precious family
都有珍貴的家人
and their livelihood.
和他們的生計
President.
社長
Otsuka.
大塚
Everyone…
大家
Boss…
社長
let's start all over again.
讓我們重新來過
We are all ready to
我們所有人都準備好了
follow you.
要追隨社長
I'm sorry.
對不起
I promise.
我保證
I'll start all over again.
我會重新來過
We can
我們可以
trust him, right?
信任他吧？
Yeah.
是啊
RESTAURANT HANASAKI
（花咲居酒屋）
-Good work, both of you. -Thank you.
-你們兩個都辛苦了 -謝謝
Thanks.
謝謝
I reported to the top about Deputy Branch Manager Wakamura.
我向高層報告了若村副理的事
And about Tokyo Dallas too.
還有關於東京達拉斯的事
I wonder what will happen to Tokyo Dallas?
真不知道東京達拉斯會怎樣？
I think they'll have to close down their business.
我想他們不得不結束生意一次
You're right.
你說的對
But if he's really determined,
但是，如果真的有決心
he can rebuild it.
他大可重新把生意做起來
Yes.
對
This is delicious.
這個好好吃
When you make something delicious,
當你做出好吃的東西
the customer smiles,
顧客露出笑容
and thanks you for the food.
謝謝你所做的食物
He'll be fine as long as he doesn't forget that feeling.
他會沒事的，只要他不忘記那種感覺
Okay.
對
I have a new dish.
我有一道新菜色
-What? -A new dish?
-什麼？ -新菜色？
We won't expand our location,
我們不展店
but we have new dishes.
但是我們有新菜色
I see. I want to try it.
這樣啊，我想吃吃看
Here it is.
在這裡
Hanasaki style Japanese beef grilled with miso and pepper.
花咲式和牛，以味噌和胡椒燒烤
Steak?
牛排？
You don't like it?
你們不喜歡嗎？
It's not that I don't like it.
我不是不喜歡
Try to place yourself in our shoes.
你設身處地幫我們想一想嘛
But it looks delicious.
可是，看起來好好吃
-I'll try it. -You're eating it?
-我要吃了 -你在吃了？
Yeah.
對
Then I will too.
那我也要
Delicious!
好好吃
It's so good.
太好吃了
Right?
對吧？
This goes well with sake. Let's have a drink.
那個和清酒很搭，我們喝一杯
Thanks.
謝謝
Can you make some more?
你可以多做一點嗎？
-Two more? -Sounds good.
-再兩份？ -好喔
As for the incident at the Shinagawa Branch…
至於品川分行事件
The person accepting the bribe from a customer,
收取客戶賄款的人
was Deputy Branch Manager Wakamura.
是若村副理
I see.
我了解了
I can't believe a deputy branch manager
不敢相信一個分行副理
took part in fraud.
參與詐騙
He needs to be punished.
他需要接受懲處
Yes! But…
是，不過…
I believe Branch Manager Yagi will also
我相信分行經理八木
have to take responsibility.
也必須負起責任
All because of a foolish subordinate
只因為一個愚蠢
who doesn't know his place.
不知分際的下屬
It's extremely unfair that the future of someone capable is threatened
一個有才幹的人前途因此受到威脅
because of this.
太不公平了
Yes.
是
In order to pull together the people within our company,
為了團結公司內部的人
I'll need to push forward
我需要推動
with my reform.
我的改革
Even if I have to do so in a rough manner.
即使必須採取粗暴手段
At any rate,
無論如何
what an eyesore.
那兩個分行稽核班的
Those two in Branch Inspection.
真夠礙眼
BRANCH INSPECTION
（分行稽核班）
I have indigestion.
我消化不良
Just as I thought, eating steak for three days in a row…
跟我想的一樣，連著三天吃牛排
-It made me sick. -Really? You couldn't handle that?
-很難受 -真的啊，你負擔不了嗎？
How weak.
真虛弱
-Mr. Soma, you're okay? -Perfect.
-相馬先生，你沒事嗎？ -好得很
You're a foodie, after all.
畢竟你是個吃貨
You have a strong stomach.
你有一個鐵胃
-Oh. -What?
-啊！ -怎樣？
Mr. Soma, your stomach is starting to stick out.
相馬先生，你的胃開始凸出來了
What? I'm completely fine.
哪有？我好得很
Please watch your diet.
請注意你的飲食
People your age usually gain weight.
你這種年紀的人很容易發福
Then Mr. Shibasa--
那麼芝崎先生…
Who are you calling fat?
你們在說誰胖啊？
Mr. Shibasaki… no, that's not what we meant.
芝崎次長，我們不是那個意思
-Whoa. -Hanasaki, speaking of age…
-哇！ -花咲，說到年紀
My wife wanted me to show you this.
我老婆要我讓妳看這個
Wait, is this…
等等，這是…
It's your matchmaking partner.
妳的相親對象
He's an elite that graduated from Tokyo University.
他是東京大學畢業的菁英
I think he's a good match.
我認為他是很好的對象
I'm not thinking about marriage right now.
我現在不考慮結婚
At least take a look at it.
至少看一下
No thank you.
不用，謝謝你
Thank you. All right, let's write the report.
感謝你，我們來寫報告吧
-Are you sure? -Look.
-妳確定嗎？ -你看
-Wow. He's pretty good looking. -Right?
-他長得很帥呢 -對吧？
He'll be a hard worker.
他會是努力工作的人
He'll make lots of money. Definitely a billion a year.
他會賺很多錢，一年肯定有十億
Can I…
我可以…
take a little look?
看一下嗎？
You said you won't look.
妳說妳不看的
I want to look at it now. Isn't that an improvement?
我現在想看了，不是很好嗎？
-No. -Wait.
-不行 -等等
-Why? -Stop being immature.
-為什麼？ -別像小學生一樣
Matchmaking?
相親？
-Keihin Bank collapsed! -Collapsed?
-京濱銀行倒閉了 -倒閉？
What about my money?
我的錢怎麼辦？
It's precious money that supported Ms. Shizue.
那些錢對靜枝女士很重要 因為它就像幸運符那樣保護她
It's her fault for being conned.
她被騙是她的錯
I'm so sorry.
對不起
I will never forgive you.
我絕對不原諒你
Subtitle translation by: Lili Morita
字幕翻譯：李怡樸